

HARD SKILLS

PHP
LARAVEL
HTML
MVC
MYSQL
ANGULAR JS
JAVASCRIPT
GITHUB
NODE.JS
WORDPRESS
CSS
IONIC
VS CODE

SOFT SKILLS

Team player Communication Creative spirit Leadership Active learning Critical thinking

LANGUAGES

French-native
English-proficient
Luxembourgish-beginner

ACTIVITIES

Brazilian JIU-JITSU(Brown Belt) Instructor & Competitor Music Travel

INFOS

P: +352 691 443 222 E: aitisham@gmail.com Nationality: FRENCH Driver's licence B @github.com/isham-it @linkedin.com/in/hicham-ait-lachgar

HICHAM AIT LACHGAR

<>JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER</>

MY BACKGROUND

After years in the food industry, I decided to change my professional career following the evolution of the digital world. I have a good sense of priorities, also experience in team management, I have ambition and I am driven by results. I have a great desire to learn and succeed in the web development sector in order to invest myself with passion.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP "CODING JOB"

BY NUMERICALL, BELVAL, LUXEMBOURG
MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021
BOOTCAMP INTENSIVE TRAINING "CODING JOBS" OF 490 HOURS OVER 5
MONTHS. DEVELOP THE MOST-VALUED TECH SKILLS OF FRONT-END AND BACK-END. GAIN EXPERTISE IN FRAMEWORKS SUCH AS ANGULAR JS FOR FRONT-END AND LARAVEL, MVC, MYSQL FOR BACK-END.

TRAINING PROGRAM "CODE START"

BY NUMERICALL, WALFERDANGE, LUXEMBOURG MARCH 2021 (2 WEEKS)
LEARN HOW TO CREATE A HTML&CSS SIMPLE WEBSITE.
LEARN THE BASICS OF JAVASCRIPT LANGUAGE.

• ACCOUTING TRAINING 'HELP ACCOUNTANT'

LUXEMBOURG LIFELONG LEARNING CENTER SEPTEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2021

• BACCALAUREATE ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING
1997

WORK EXPERIENCE

FOOD STORE & RETAIL MANAGER

- KAEMPFF-KOHLER (LUXEMBOURG) MARCH 2011-FEBRUARY 2021
 Train and manage a team of 5 in-store employees.
 In charge of overall store operations.
 Buyer from suppliers in Europe.
 Assist customers in all aspects of store service.
- SUSHI SHOP (PARIS) MAY 2010-DECEMBER 2010
- FROMAGERIE 31 (PARIS) NOVEMBER 2002-APRIL 2010
- BAKERY MANAGER (PARIS) AUGUST 2000-SEPTEMBER 2002
- SALESMAN (RUNGIS) OCTOBER 1997- JUNE 2000